A visitor.
Hmm.
Indeed, I have slept long enough.
The Kingdom of Heaven has
long since forgotten my name.
And I am eager to make them remember.
However, the blood of Motherless stays changing.
And I must admit, I'm curious about your skills.
Will it?
And soon, before I take down this
disk and crush the armies of Heaven,
you shall do as ever can.
Come forth, Child of Heaven
AND DIE
You can't escape.
NICE TRY
YES!!
THAT IT!!
DESTROY
This will hurt
You can't escape.
NICE TRY
KEEP IT
DESTROY
This prison to hold.
So for the life and time of the princess.
A fitting end to an
existence defined by futile struggle.
Don't look for the very side.
And I don't regret the second of it.
[Laughter]